<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shubham Singh</title>
    <link>http://shubham-singh.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shubham Singh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 13:13:37 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://shubham-singh.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Side Template Injection with Flask and Jinja2</title>
      <link>http://shubham-singh.me/posts/server-side-template-injection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 13:13:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shubham-singh.me/posts/server-side-template-injection/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Last week I took part in a CTF, and one of the problems from the &amp;ldquo;Web&amp;rdquo; category seems pretty intriguing to me. Although I was able to get the Flag, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t submit the flag in time, so no points for me 😔.
The interesting thing about this problem was, that the technology which needed to be exploited was something I am pretty familiar with and had a lot of experience in, but still, even after working with that tech stack for years, I was unaware of this vulnerability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DGTOnline</title>
      <link>http://shubham-singh.me/projects/dgtonline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 19:12:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shubham-singh.me/projects/dgtonline/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of my freelance projects, DGTOnline is a platform for a Mumbai based competitive exam coaching center. The main purpose of this platform was to provide a simple and easy to use interface that could help the faculty at the institution to easily conduct test with more accuracy and more frequency. At the same time the platform would help students to get accustomed to web based testing portals for these competitive examinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Automation in Whatsapp</title>
      <link>http://shubham-singh.me/projects/message-automation-in-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 16:28:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shubham-singh.me/projects/message-automation-in-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of my freelance projects was at a coaching institute which needed to automate the process of sending daily timetables to their students. Up until this point, someone had to manually forward the daily schedule to students sometimes in a group and sometimes even individually to up to 150-200 students. Even students from the same class can have different classes each day due to remedial classes, reassessment examinations, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://shubham-singh.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shubham-singh.me/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an undergrad student at Gujarat Technological University, currently persuing my undergrad in Computer Engineering. I have 3+ years of experience in developing applications using web based and native technologies. I have also worked as a freelance developer and help build software based solutions for multiple local businesses.
At this site I will be sharing some of my personal projects and I will also try to post technical articles related to programming on weekly or monthly basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>